♠ Glenshaw, PA 15116

□ alex.durr@gmail.com

mww.linkedin.com/in/alexdurr

412-478-6399

github.com/adurr234

alexdurr.com

Alexander Durr

Solutions Architect / Developer

AWS Certified Solutions Architect/Developer utilizing technical training along with a long history of outstanding customer service and sales to bring cloud solutions to consumers.

Achieved all Associate level AWS Certifications. Self-motivated individual expanding depth of current skills and learning new skills daily. Exceptional history of customer service and communication. Experienced team leader and trainer.

- Amazon Web Services (AWS)
- Linux
- Windows
- Python
- Ruby
- Elastic Compute Cloud (Ec2)

- Chef Automation
- SQL/MYSQL/RDS
- Git / GitHub
- Customer Relationship Management (CRM)
- Customer Service

Certifications

Certified Solutions Architect – Associate – Amazon Web Services
Certified Developer – Associate – Amazon Web Services
Certified SysOps Administrator – Associate – Amazon Web Services
e-PRO – NAR

Experience

Real Estate Agent – Re/Max Realty Brokers – 2006 – 2017

Real Estate Agent – Prudential Preferred Realty – 2004 – 2006

Professional Internet Gaming/Poker - Independent - 2001 - 2005

Financial Assistant – Carnegie Mellon University – 2000 – 2002

Education

B.S. Business Administration, Computer Information Systems – *Thomas Edison State University* – 2016 – 2017

Business Administration - Carnegie Mellon University - 1998 - 2002